Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Peter E. Palmquist papers
1822-2003
1952-2003
WA MSS S-2965
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
77.5
(213 boxes) + 21 broadsides.
Papers and related material documenting Peter Palmquist's roles as a collector and historian of photography, as well as a photographer, 1952-2003. Material includes correspondence, writings, research files, printed material, photographs, audiovisual material, and electronic files.
Palmquist, Peter E.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Peter Palmquist and the Estate of Peter Palmquist on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana and Walter McClintock Memorial Fund, 2003-2004.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 221-228 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Boxes 229-234 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Associated Materials
The Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University, has several collections assembled by Peter Palmquist.
Biographical information and photographic materials related to women photographers are included in the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography (WA MSS S-2600). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Photographs created by Peter Palmquist are included in the Peter Palmquist Photographs (WA Photos 524). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Biographical information and photographic materials related to male photographers active in the western United States are included in the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Male Photographers in the American West (WA MSS S-2733). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Biographical information and photographic materials related to male photographers active in Humboldt County, California, are included in the Peter Palmquist Collection of Humboldt County, California, Male Photographers (WA MSS S-2670). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Cased photographs are included in the Peter Palmquist Cased Photographs Collection (WA Photos 402). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Unique and rare photographic formats collected by Palmquist are in the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Photography and Photographic Formats (WA Photos 490). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Stereograph cards that depict California are included in the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Stereographs of California (WA Photos 494). Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Yale University.
Books and periodicals formerly in the personal library of Peter Palmquist are accessible via the library catalog by searching for: "Palmquist, Peter E., Ownership."
Peter E. Palmquist (1936-2003)
A photographer, collector, and historian of photography, Peter Eric Palmquist was born in Oakland, California on September 23, 1936. In 1944, he moved with his family to Ferndale, California, and he spent most of his life in Humboldt County. During adolescence, Palmquist trained himself in photography. He served in the United States Army as a photographer from 1955 to 1959, mainly with the Supreme Headquarters Allied Powers Europe in Paris, France. Palmquist worked briefly as a photographer for the state government of California from 1959 to 1961. From 1961 until his retirement in 1989, Palmquist worked as a staff photographer for Humboldt State University, Arcata, California, where he also graduated with a Bachelor of Arts degree in Art in 1965.
From 1971 until his death, Palmquist collected textual materials and hundreds of thousands of photographic items documenting the practice and occupation of photography from its beginning through the turn of the twenty-first century. He had particular interest in early California photographers, photographers of the American West, and women photographers.
A self-trained researcher and historian of photography, Palmquist organized more than one hundred exhibitions and wrote more than three hundred articles and a hundred monographs. He was a founding editor of The Daguerreian Annual, and a president of the National Stereoscopic Association.
Palmquist died January 13, 2003, in Oakland.
Scope and Contents
Papers and related material documenting Peter Palmquist's roles as a collector and historian of photography, as well as a photographer, 1952-2003. Material includes correspondence, writings, research files, printed material, photographs, audiovisual material, and electronic files.
The collection, which reflects the order of Palmquist's papers at the time of his death, includes research files on a range of subjects containing material from circa 1848 to 2003, with a focus on photography, especially its role in the history of the American West, particularly in California. The research files also provide rich documentation for the history of Humboldt County, California, the birthplace and primary residence of Palmquist. In most of the research files, the order of the materials reflects the original filing order used by Palmquist.
Correspondence documents the working relationships between Palmquist and auction houses, filmmakers, gallery owners, geographers, historians, historical societies, libraries, museums, photographers, and publishers related chiefly to the history of photography.
The papers include examples of academic articles and photographs published by Palmquist, as well as research files and drafts related to his publications and projects, including unrealized efforts. Exhibition material includes preparatory and publicity material, as well as documentation of shows that Palmquist designed or participated in.
Arrangement
Organized into nine series: I. Correspondence, 1970-2003. II. Publications and Publicity, 1960-2003. III. Material for Publications and Exhibitions, 1901-2003. IV. General Research Files, 1822-2002. V. Collection Inventories, 1985-1994. Series VI. Business Records, 1962-1964. VII. Oversize Material, 1851-2002. VIII. Audiovisual Material, 1964-2003. IX. Electronic Files, 1982-2003.
Cities and towns -- California -- Pictorial works; Photographers -- History; Photographers -- California; Photographers -- West (U.S.); Photography -- History; Photography -- California; Photography -- West (U.S.); California -- Pictorial works; Humboldt County (Calif.); Humboldt County (Calif.) -- Pictorial works; West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Palmquist, Peter E.
- Correspondence, 1970-2003; Series I; 11.7 linear feet (44 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Organized into six subseries: Bound Volumes, 1970-1989; Bound Volumes, 1990-1992; Bound Volumes, 1993-1998; Unbound Correspondence and Research; Correspondence Files; and Working Files.
  Scope and Contents
  This subseries consists chiefly of correspondence received by Palmquist between 1970 and 1998, which he arranged alphabetically by correspondent and then bound into volumes, as well as unbound correspondence, 1978-2002, the bulk of which date from 1990 to 2002.
  - Bound Volumes, 1970-1989
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume I: Aa-Barb, 1970-1989 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume II: Barg-Bz, 1970-1989 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume III: Ca-Chas, 1970-1989 (Box 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IV: Chi-Coke, 1970-1989 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume V: Col-Dz, 1970-1989 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VI: Ea-Fz, 1970-1989 (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VII: Ga-Heng, 1970-1989 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VIII: Heni-Hug, 1970-1989 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IX: Hum-Hz, 1970-1989 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume X: Ia-Jz, 1970-1989 (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XI: Ka-Lz, 1970-1989 (Box 11)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XII: Ma-Mz, 1970-1989 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XIII: Na-Pet, 1970-1989 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XIV: Pet-Rz, 1970-1989 (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XV: Sa-Sim, 1970-1989 (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XVI: Sis-Sz, 1970-1989 (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XVII: Ta-Wein, 1970-1989 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XVIII: Wein-Zz, 1970-1989 (Box 18)
  - Bound Volumes, 1990-1992
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume I: Aa-Bz, 1990-1992 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume II: Ca-Dem, 1990-1992 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume III: Deu-Gre, 1990-1992 (Box 21)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IV: Ha-Jon, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume V: Jos-Mar, 1990-1992 (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VI: Mat-Pea, 1990-1992 (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VII: Peck-Rz, 1990-1992 (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VIII: Sak-Tz, 1990-1992 (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IX: Und-Zz, 1990-1992 (Box 27)
  - Bound Volumes, 1993-1998
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume I: Abb-Cal, 1993-1998 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume II: Cal-Dem, 1993-1998 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume III: Dem-Get, 1993-1998 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IV: Gia-Har, 1993-1998 (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume V: Har-Hun, 1993-1998 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VI: Ida-Kas, 1993-1998 (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VII: Kel-McL, 1993-1998 (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume VIII: McW-Noy, 1993-1998 (Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume IX: Oak-Pri, 1993-1998 (Box 36)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume X: Prz-Sim, 1993-1998 (Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XI: Sin-Uni, 1993-1998 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Volume XII: Va-Z, 1993-1998 (Box 39)
  - Unbound Correspondence and Research
    Correspondence and related research prepared by Palmquist and his assistants for binding into volumes, which he designated as "Correspondence and Research."
    - Correspondence and Research, 1991 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1993 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1994 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1995 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1996 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1997; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1998; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Correspondence and Research, 1999 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence and Research, 2000 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence and Research, 2001 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence and Research, 2002 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence and Research, 2003 (Box 41)
  - Correspondence Files
    Arranged alphabetically.
    Correspondence to Palmquist.
    - Abbeville Press, 1999 October-2000 September (Box 42)
    - Adams-Graf, John, 1999 March (Box 42)
    - Anaya, Stephen, 2000 January (Box 42)
    - Anderson, Kat, 2002 July (Box 42)
    - Anderson, Erick, 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Andrew Smith Gallery, 1996 April-2002 October (Box 42)
    - Aperture, 1999 September (Box 42)
    - Appollo, Ken, 1999 October (Box 42)
    - Autry Museum, 2002 May (Box 42)
    - Bailey, Richard, undated (Box 42)
    - Barisdale, Roger G., 1998 February (Box 42)
    - Bancroft Library, 1999 September-2000 November (Box 42)
    - Barnum, Kate, 1999 December-2000 January (Box 42)
    - Barrie, Sandy, 1999 February-2001 September (Box 42)
    - Bartley, Sylvia, 2001 March (Box 42)
    - Beck, Kisten, 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Beck, Randy, undated (Box 42)
    - Becker, Bill, 1996 August (Box 42)
    - Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 1998 November-2002 November (Box 42)
    - Bellows, Joseph, 1998 October (Box 42)
    - Bennet, Gordon, 1999 September (Box 42)
    - Berrien, Gay, 1998 November-2000 September (Box 42)
    - Berry, Tracy, undated (Box 42)
    - Bishop, Joan, 2002 July (Box 42)
    - Bishop, Ray, 2002 June (Box 42)
    - Blackburn, Tom, undated (Box 42)
    - Borgo Press, undated (Box 42)
    - Boyling, Mary Ellen, 2002 January (Box 42)
    - BRC Imagination Arts, 1999 July (Box 42)
    - British Columbia Archives, 2000 January (Box 42)
    - Brizard Company, 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Brogden, Penny, 2001 February (Box 42)
    - Brown, Julie K., 1999 January-December (Box 42)
    - Bruck, E. Kergan, 1999 September (Box 42)
    - Bruckmayr, Dave, 1999 September (Box 42)
    - Bruffee, Byron, undated (Box 42)
    - Burgess, Jo Ann, 1999 January-2000 April (Box 42)
    - Burke, Quentin, 1999 July (Box 42)
    - Burton-Caravajal, Julianne, 2001 March-July (Box 42)
    - Butterfields, undated (Box 42)
    - Cachuma Press, 1999 July (Box 42)
    - California Historical Society, 1999 April-2002 June (Box 42)
    - California State Library, 1996 July (Box 42)
    - Canadian Centre for Architecture, 1995 May (Box 42)
    - Carroll, David, 2000 December (Box 42)
    - Chinn, Becky, 2000 April (Box 42)
    - Chris, Alex, 1999 March-April (Box 42)
    - Clay, Jackie, undated (Box 42)
    - Clio, Inc., 1999 May-2002 November (Box 42)
    - Cook, Francis, 1983 March (Box 42)
    - Cooper, Victoria, 2000 December (Box 42)
    - Cowan, Chester, undated (Box 42)
    - Crabtree Publishing Co., 1999 March (Box 42)
    - Craig, Will, 2002 April (Box 42)
    - Daguerreian Society, undated (Box 42)
    - Darlymaple, Larry, 2000 March (Box 42)
    - Darrah, William Culp, 1981 December-1982 January (Box 42)
    - Davis, Bruce, 1998 August- October (Box 42)
    - Dawson, Rolf, 2000 January (Box 42)
    - DeBella, Dave, undated (Box 42)
    - Delaware Historical Society, 2000 May (Box 42)
    - Denny, Margaret, 2001 March-2002 August (Box 42)
    - Dillon, Dick, 2002 January (Box 42)
    - Drake, Greg, 2001 February-2002 February (Box 42)
    - Erickson, Bruce, undated (Box 42)
    - Esau, Erika, 2001 May (Box 42)
    - Eskind, Andrew, 1999 October (Box 42)
    - Eureka Printing, 1999 July (Box 42)
    - Evans, Bruce, 2000 March (Box 42)
    - Ewer, Gary, 1996 November (Box 42)
    - Farmer, David, undated (Box 42)
    - Faye, Ted, 1998 February (Box 42)
    - First Street Gallery, 2001 July (Box 42)
    - Fisher, Ken, 1999 March- September (Box 42)
    - Florentine Films, 1998 December-1999 May (Box 42)
    - Fraenkel Gallery, 1998 December (Box 42)
    - Gale Group, 2000 January (Box 42)
    - Garcia, Erin, 2000 June (Box 42)
    - George Eastman House, 1999 January (Box 42)
    - Getty Museum, 1992 October-2002 December; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Gilbert, George, 2000 May-June (Box 42)
    - Gottheim, Larry, 2000 July (Box 42)
    - Graf, John, 1989 August-1995 September; 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Groves, Eugene, 2001 June (Box 42)
    - Guggenheim Foundation, 2000 November (Box 42)
    - Hammond, Anne, 1999 June- October (Box 42)
    - Hammond, Joyce, 1999 May (Box 42)
    - Harper, Mary Alice, 1999 June (Box 42)
    - Hansen, Miriam, 2000 March (Box 42)
    - Hertzmann, Paul, 1999 August (Box 42)
    - Heyday Books, 1998 December-2001 September (Box 42)
    - Hill, Jane, undated (Box 42)
    - Holm-Johnsen, Hanne, 1999 December (Box 42)
    - Hooper, Bruce, 1994 November (Box 42)
    - Houston Center for Photography, 1999 January-October (Box 42)
    - Howe, Kathleen Stewart, 2001 July (Box 42)
    - Hughes, Edan, undated (Box 42)
    - Hult-Lewis, Christine, 1999 May (Box 42)
    - Humboldt Art Council, 2000 January-2002 February (Box 42)
    - Humboldt County Historical Society, 1999 February-2001 February (Box 42)
    - Humboldt State University Library, 1999 February-2000 June (Box 42)
    - Hunter Museum of American Art, 2000 May-July (Box 42)
    - The Huntington Library, Art Collections and Botanical Gardens, 1995 February (Box 42)
    - Ihara, Rachel, 2000 June (Box 42)
    - Instituto Moreira Salles, 2000 August (Box 42)
    - Ink People, 2000 December-2002 July (Box 42)
    - Institute for Historical Study, 1998-2002 (Box 42)
    - International Museum of Women, 1998-2002 (Box 42)
    - International Photography Hall of Fame, 1998 October-2002 Spring (Box 42)
    - Irvin, Ronald D., 2002 October (Box 42)
    - Jensen, James, 1999 February-2001 July (Box 42)
    - Jezierski, John, 2000 May- 2001 December (Box 42)
    - Johnson, Charles, 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Jones, Elizabeth, 2001 December (Box 42)
    - Joseph, Stern, 1999 August-2001 March (Box 42)
    - Journal of the West, 2001 April-2002 January (Box 42)
    - Kailbourn, Tom, 1990 August-2001 April (Box 42)
    - Kolbe, Bob, 1999 March (Box 42)
    - Knight, Kathy, undated (Box 42)
    - Knoblock, Steve, 1996 April (Box 42)
    - KQED, 2000 December (Box 42)
    - Kugler, Richard C., 2000 September-2000 November (Box 42)
    - Kunhardt Productions, Inc., 2002 December -2003 February (Box 42)
    - Lai, Edwin, 1997 December-2002 August (Box 42)
    - Lapp, Marshall, 2001 April (Box 42)
    - Latour, Ira, 2000 January- February (Box 42)
    - Lee, Mack, April 2002 (Box 42)
    - Lehr, Janet, 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Leland, Dorothy K., 1999 February (Box 42)
    - Levine, Lynn, 1999 October (Box 42)
    - Lewis, Gary D., 2001 October (Box 42)
    - The Library of Congress, Prints and Photographs Division, 1996 August (Box 42)
    - Loeffler, Jane, 2000 January (Box 42)
    - Lowe, Gary D., 1998 May (Box 42)
    - Lowry, Bates, 2000 November-2001 April (Box 42)
    - Luchetti, Cathy, 2000 April (Box 42)
    - Macauley, Cameron, 2000 September (Box 43)
    - Malinick, Cindi, 2001 February (Box 43)
    - MacGregor, Bruce, 1997 August-2000 July (Box 43)
    - Marien, Mary Lou, 1999 March-2002 December (Box 43)
    - Martino, Jules A., 2001 November (Box 43)
    - Marunias, Nathaniel, 1999 March (Box 43)
    - Mason, Glenn, 2001 April-July (Box 43)
    - Mattison, David, 1999 March-2000 October (Box 43)
    - Mautz, Carl, 1997 November-2001 June (Box 43)
    - McCarroll, Stacey, 2002 June (Box 43)
    - McComiskey, Nora, 2001 July (Box 43)
    - McHenry Museum, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - McKeena, Maureen, 2001 October (Box 43)
    - McLame, Bobbie, 2000 May (Box 43)
    - Meister, Laura, 2001 April (Box 43)
    - Menkes, Dove, 2002 November (Box 43)
    - Mertes, Cara, 2000 February-2001 February (Box 43)
    - Minnesota Historical Society, 1999 January-September (Box 43)
    - Mimms, Liz, 2000 June (Box 43)
    - Montana Historical Society, 1996 June (Box 43)
    - Moore, Sharon, 1995 December (Box 43)
    - Morrill, Apollonia, 2000 June- December (Box 43)
    - Naef, Weston, 1999 June (Box 43)
    - National Library of Wales, 1999 July (Box 43)
    - Nearpass, Kate, 1989 February (Box 43)
    - Nevada State Railroad Museum, 1994 August-October (Box 43)
    - Olarsch, Leonard, 1998 March (Box 43)
    - Osterman, Mark (Box 43)
    - Pajerski, Fred, 1999 January-2002 November (Box 43)
    - Palmquist, Erin, 2000 May (Box 43)
    - Parish, Susan, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - Patterson, Charlene, 1999 August (Box 43)
    - Paull, Coralee, 2000 August-2002 February (Box 43)
    - Peluso, Tony, 1999 December-2001 February (Box 43)
    - Pepin, Douglas, 2000 March (Box 43)
    - Pequignot, Karen, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - Pero, Thomas, 1999 July (Box 43)
    - Perry, Claire, 1999 January-2002 July (Box 43)
    - Paterson, Christian, 1999 April (Box 43)
    - Pfaelzer, Jeannie, 2001 May (Box 43)
    - Philbrick, Kate, 2000 September (Box 43)
    - Photographic Canadiana, 1999 February (Box 43)
    - Photo Review, 2001 Fall- 2002 Winter (Box 43)
    - P. R. C., Winter 1999-Winter/Spring 2001 (Box 43)
    - Piwarzyk, Robert, undated (Box 43)
    - Plowden, David, undated (Box 43)
    - Polk, Milbry, 1998 November-2002 September (Box 43)
    - Price, Doug, 2002 September -2003 February (Box 43)
    - Rayfield, Beth, 1997 October- November (Box 43)
    - Regrev, Hanna, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - Ressler, Susan, 2000 May (Box 43)
    - Rinhart, Floyd and Marion, 1990 November-1991 August (Box 43)
    - Rodriguez, Gina, 1999 March (Box 43)
    - Rudisill, Richard, 1996 December-2001 March (Box 43)
    - Salem Press, 1993 November-1994 September (Box 43)
    - Sammut, Deborah, 1999 July (Box 43)
    - Sandweiss, Martha, 1981, 1999 March-2002 June (Box 43)
    - San Francisco Historical Society, 1996 May-1998 December (Box 43)
    - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1994 October-1999 February (Box 43)
    - Schiesari, Nancy, 1998 April (Box 43)
    - Schinto, Jeanne, 2001 May-2002 November (Box 43)
    - Schwie, Dale, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - Secrest, William, 2000 December-2001 May (Box 43)
    - Shafer, Paul, 1999 January-October (Box 43)
    - Shaw, Jennifer, 1997 May-1998 March (Box 43)
    - Sims, Perry, 2002 May (Box 43)
    - Smith, Bruce M., 2001 June (Box 43)
    - Society for Photographic Education, 2003 March (Box 43)
    - Sioux City Public Library, 1978 March (Box 43)
    - Siskiyou County Museum, 1999 January-2000 January (Box 43)
    - Society of California Pioneers, 2001 January (Box 43)
    - Solem, Borge, 2000 October (Box 43)
    - Solmssen, Peter, 2000 December (Box 43)
    - Solnit, Rebecca, 2001 May (Box 43)
    - Sotheby's, 2000 July- August (Box 43)
    - Southern Oregon Historical Society, 1999 September-2000 August (Box 43)
    - Sprague, Gloria, 1999 August (Box 43)
    - Staas, John W., 1999 May (Box 43)
    - Stacey, Robert, November 1990 (Box 43)
    - Stanford University Press, 1999 September-May 2003 (Box 43)
    - Storch, Richard, 2002 October (Box 43)
    - Street, Richard S., 1998 December-2002 July (Box 43)
    - Stohlman, Rachel, 2003 January (Box 43)
    - Swann Gallery, 1999 May (Box 43)
    - Taylor, Roger, 2000 September (Box 43)
    - Ten Speed Press, 1999 June (Box 43)
    - Thompson, Karen (Pequignot), 1999 December (Box 43)
    - Timby, Kim, 2001 January (Box 43)
    - Tinder, Dave, 1993 May-2002 October (Box 43)
    - Tippett, Verna, undated (Box 43)
    - Treadwell, Tex, 1999 March (Box 43)
    - Toth, Dennis, 2000 November (Box 43)
    - Troup, Alexander, undated (Box 43)
    - Troy, Tim, 1999 December (Box 43)
    - Tulare Historical Museum, 1999 December (Box 43)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 2000 June (Box 43)
    - University of California, 2001 January (Box 43)
    - University of Oklahoma Press, 1997 January-1999 January (Box 43)
    - University of Utah Press, undated (Box 43)
    - Vanek, Andrea, 2000 June (Box 43)
    - Van Zante, Gary, 2001 September -2002 August (Box 43)
    - Ventura County Museum, August 1995 (Box 43)
    - Wajda, Shirley, 1996 July-November (Box 43)
    - Walle, Leonard A., 1996 September (Box 43)
    - Wallentine, Ellis, 1999 February (Box 43)
    - Walters, David, 1999 March (Box 43)
    - Walton, Krys and Bill, 1994 December (Box 43)
    - Ware, Susan, 2000 December (Box 43)
    - Watts, Jenny, 1999 January-2001 May (Box 43)
    - Werks, 2002 October (Box 43)
    - Wertcliffe Publisher, undated (Box 43)
    - Wilsted and Taylor, 1999 March-2000 September (Box 43)
    - Wimmer, Ted, 1985 September (Box 43)
    - Wolfe, Richard I., 1990 January (Box 43)
    - Women of the West, 1998 November (Box 43)
    - Women in Photography International, undated (Box 43)
    - Wood, David, 2000 January-February (Box 43)
    - Woodruff, Ann, 2001 September (Box 43)
    - Woodrum, Barbara, 2003 January (Box 43)
    - Wulzen. Frank E., 1998 February (Box 43)
    - Wyatt, 2002 June (Box 43)
    - Wyller, Elin, 1999 November (Box 43)
    - Young, Joe, June 1998-2002 December (Box 43)
    - Zogg, Dell (Box 43)
    - Zoss, Betty Hurwich, 1997 October (Box 43)